                  <News>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-13T16:16:27-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>ICIS News</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>MOVES: US Chevron Phillips names new vp of research &amp; technology</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Don Lycette has been appointed senior vice president, research and technology, US-based Chevron Phillips Chemical announced on Thursday.  Lycette will begin his tenure on 1 May and will be replacing Dennis Holtermann, who is retiring after 33 years with Chevron Phillips and Chevron, the company said.</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.icis.com/Articles/2014/03/13/9762759/moves-us-chevron-phillips-names-new-vp-of-research.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-13T15:48:40-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Nine O'Clock</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>President Basescu meets Chevron, ExxonMobil and Petrom officials</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Among other things, there have been talks about the importance of the transfer to Romania of Chevron&#39;s shale gas know-how from the US as a contribution to the development.

President Traian Basescu on Thursday welcomed Chevron Europe Exploration and Production General Manager Derek Magness to discuss the transfer of Chevron&#39;s shale gas know-how from the US to Romania. ‘At the meeting,</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.nineoclock.ro/president-basescu-meets-chevron-exxonmobil-and-petrom-officials/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-13T12:34:25-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Argus Media Limited</SourceDescription>
                         <CategoryText>Executive Activity</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron's olefins growth at 10mn t/yr by 2017</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Houston, 12 March (Argus) &#8212; Chevron&#39;s global production of ethylene, polyethylene and polypropylene is set to grow from 8mn t/yr to more than 10mn t/yr by 2017, according to an investor presentation this week.

Much of the gains come from the company&#39;s North American segment, where an abundance of cheap NGL feedstocks is driving investments in further olefins capacity.

“Changing</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.argusmedia.com/News/Article?id=893769</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-13T11:13:07-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Business Wire</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Announcement</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Phillips Chemical Announces New Senior Vice President of Research &amp; Technology</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>THE WOODLANDS, Texas--( BUSINESS WIRE )--Chevron Phillips Chemical Company LLC (Chevron Phillips Chemical) is pleased to announce that effective May 1, 2014, Don Lycette has been appointed senior vice president, research and technology, replacing Dennis Holtermann who has elected to retire after 33 years of distinguished service with Chevron Phillips Chemical and Chevron Corporation.

?</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20140313005261/en</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-13T10:53:33-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Mining Australia</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Activity</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Gorgon LNG project on schedule</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron&#39;s Gorgon project is 80 per cent complete and on track to deliver first gas in the second half of 2015.

In an investor conference, the company also said 65 per cent of the LNG to be produced from the project had been committed under long-term contracts.

Chevron&#39;s second major gas project in WA, Wheatstone, has 82 per cent of its gas committed and is 30 per cent complete.

?</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.miningaustralia.com.au/news/gorgon-lng-project-on-schedule</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-13T10:01:56-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>The Jakarta Post</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron to relocate employee</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>PT Chevron Pacific Indonesia (CPI), the local subsidiary of US-based oil company Chevron, plans to relocate the families of its employees from areas affected by air pollution from land fires, to avoid negative health effects.

“Chevron plans to relocate those who seem to be at high risk of developing haze-related problems -- such as newborns, pregnant women, children under five years old</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.thejakartapost.com/news/2014/03/13/chevron-relocate-employee-families-affected-haze.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-13T03:02:28-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Mining Weekly</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron considering $10bn Gorgon expansion</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Energy major Chevron is considering a $10-billion expansion of its Gorgon liquefied natural gas (LNG) project, with senior VP for upstream  Jay Johnson  saying that the company is investigating the possibility of a fourth train.</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.miningweekly.com/article/chevron-considering-10bn-gorgon-expansion-2014-03-13</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T23:05:07-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Oil &amp; Gas Financial Journal</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>New Alliance</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Atlas Pipeline Partners to review ownership interest in WTXLPG</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Atlas Pipeline Partners LP (NYSE: APL) has retained Citigroup Global Markets Inc. to begin a strategic review of its ownership interest in the West Texas LPG Pipeline Limited Partnership (WTXLPG). To the extent that Atlas Pipeline executes any transaction, the potential proceeds will be used to fund part of its significant growth opportunities in its core operating areas.

WTXLPG owns a?</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.ogfj.com/articles/2014/03/atlas-pipeline-partners-to-review-ownership-interest-in-wtxlpg.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T19:20:05-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Reuters</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron warns California carbon rules will make gasoline too costly</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>NEW YORK, March 12 Wed Mar 12, 2014 7:13pm EDT

NEW YORK, March 12 (Reuters) - Pending California carbon regulations could make it too expensive to operate refineries in the most populous U.S. state, drastically increasing gasoline prices and costing thousands of jobs, a senior Chevron Corp executive said.

The No. 2 U.S. oil company, which runs California's two largest refineries,</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.reuters.com/article/2014/03/12/chevron-california-idUSL2N0M81FN20140312</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T16:24:34-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Drilling Contractor</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Drilling &amp; Completions Tech Digest</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron, GE form alliance for technology development

Chevron Energy Technology Co and GE Oil &amp; Gas have created the Chevron GE Technology Alliance, which will develop and commercialize technologies to solve critical issues for the oil and gas industry. The project will leverage research and development from GE&#39;s new Global Research Center, the first dedicated to oil and gas</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.drillingcontractor.org/drilling-completions-tech-digest-2-27933</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T15:21:17-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>ETF Daily News</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Corporation (CVX): Warnings Of Lingering Shifts In LNG Prices, Oil Prices</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Tara Clarke: Chevron Corporation (NYSE:CVX), the nation&#39;s second-largest oil company and the world&#39;s fourth-largest energy producer by market value, cut expectations for its 2017 production by 6.1% at its annual security analyst meeting today (Tuesday), citing a drop in LNG prices and an increase in oil prices .

Over the last several months, the petrochemical company, along with</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://etfdailynews.com/2014/03/12/chevron-corporation-cvx-warnings-of-lingering-shifts-in-lng-prices-oil-prices/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T15:21:16-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Yahoo! Finance</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Merger And Acquisition</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Lowers '17 Production Guidance</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>U.S. energy behemoth Chevron Corporation ( CVX ) reaffirmed its long-term growth strategies in its annual analyst meeting. The company also announced its divestment plans and the revised 2017 production outlook.

Chevron now expects to produce 3,100 thousand barrels of oil equivalent per day (MBoed) in 2017 against 3,300 MBoed stated earlier. The decline is primarily due to an</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/chevron-lowers-17-production-guidance-190007165.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T13:05:43-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Proactive Investors - North America</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron activity in Argentina builds attractive proposition for Madalena Energy</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>On an investor day conference call yesterday, Mackie Research analyst Bill Newman said Chevron made some positive comments on the shale potential in Argentina, announcing plans to drill four wells targeting the Vaca Muerta shale on its El Trapial block, which is directly east of Madalena's prized Curamhuele block.

Chevron 's ( NYSE:CVX ) news that it is planning to drill four more wells</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.proactiveinvestors.com/companies/news/52700/chevron-activity-in-argentina-builds-attractive-proposition-for-madalena-energy-52700.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T11:02:12-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Marcellus Drilling News</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron CEO Says Marcellus Drilling Scaled Back Due to Low Price</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>When the annual analyst teleconference for a big oil company is forecast to go 2.5-3 hours long, you know the news will not be good. It doesn&#39;t take that long unless you have explain and...</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://marcellusdrilling.com/2014/03/chevron-ceo-says-marcellus-drilling-scaled-back-due-to-low-price/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T11:02:43-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Interfax Global Energy Services</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Long-term deals key to Gorgon&#39;s expansion – Chevron</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>An aerial view of the Gorgon Plant under construction. Startup has slipped to mid-2015. (Chevron)

Chevron&#39;s expected start date for the $54 billion Gorgon LNG project is Australia has slipped back again to mid-2015, but the United States

operator is still looking at the potential to eventually add a fourth train, executives have said.

The three-train, 15.6 mtpa foundation</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://interfaxenergy.com/natural-gas-news-analysis/asia-pacific/long-term-deals-key-to-gorgons-expansion-chevron/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T10:43:02-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Energy Global</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron&#39;s future strategies</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron Corporation has said that it is continuing to generate industry leading operational and financial results and advancing key projects to drive future growth, at the company&#39;s annual security analyst meeting in New York.

John Watson, Chevron&#39;s Chairman and CEO said, ‘world energy demand continues to grow and the outlook for the energy business remains excellent. Our strategies</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.energyglobal.com/news/exploration/articles/Chevron_future_strategies257.aspx</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T08:28:43-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>AllAfrica.com</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Brittania-U V. Chevron - Court Fixes March 20 for Jurisdiction</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Federal High Court in Lagos has fixed March 20, 2014 to begin hearing on the application by multi-national oil firm, Chevron Group, challenging its jurisdiction to entertain the suit filed by indigenous oil exploration and production firm, Brittania-U Limited over Chevron's planned sale of Oil Mining Leases, OMLs, 52, 53 and 54.

Brittania-U is alleging that CNL and Chevron USA</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://allafrica.com/stories/201403120795.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T04:08:12-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>NEWS.com.au</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>New Alliance</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Gorgon gas 65% committed, Chevron says</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>In an investor update Chevron, the lead operator of the joint venture project, said offshore pipelaying was now complete and 65 per cent of the liquefied natural gas (LNG) from Gorgon had been committed under long-term contracts.

The cost of the energy giant's LNG project in Western Australia has blown out by $US2 billion to $US54 billion.

Also, the start-up date for first gas from</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.news.com.au/finance/business/gorgon-gas-65-committed-chevron-says/story-e6frfkur-1226852667350?from=public_rss</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T01:27:27-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>The West Australian</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron says Gorgon on track (The West Australian)</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron has told investors its biggest-ever development, the $US54 billion Gorgon LNG development, remains on track to begin producing by the middle of next year.

Speaking at its annual investor day in the US overnight, Chevron also flagged plans to sell $US10 billion of non-core assets over the next three years while conceding that it would not make its 2017 production guidance of 3.3?</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://au.news.yahoo.com/thewest/business/wa/a/21941644/chevron-says-gorgon-on-track/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-12T01:21:28-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Rigzone</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Expects its 2017 Asia Pacific Production to Be 45% Above 2013</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron Corp. expects the firm's production from Asia Pacific to rise around 45 percent to 1,000 million barrels of oil equivalent per day (MMboepd) in 2017, compared to 690 MMboepd in 2013, the company said in its presentation to the Security Analyst Meeting Tuesday.

The Gorgon LNG (liquefied natural gas) project off Western Australia is currently 78 percent completed, with 20 of 21</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.rigzone.com/news/oil_gas/a/132054/Chevron_Expects_its_2017_Asia_Pacific_Production_to_Be_45_Above_2013?rss=true</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T21:18:08-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Corporate Intelligence - The Wall Street Journal</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Wants to Export Gas. But First, the Haggling</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>A game of “chicken” is playing out in the global market for natural gas, and Chevron CEO John Watson says he isn&#39;t going to be the first to blink.</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://blogs.wsj.com/corporate-intelligence/2014/03/11/chevron-wants-to-export-gas-but-first-the-haggling/?mod=WSJBlog</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T21:03:47-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>CNBC</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron CEO tackles US energy policy</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Discussing growing oil and gas demand, and how quickly the U.S. energy businesses can meet the demand, with Chevron Chairman &amp; CEO John Watson.

Chevron plans to increase its oil and gas production by 20 percent by 2017, but most of the growth will be abroad, in part because U.S. policy isn't "pro-development," CEO John Watson told CNBC's "Closing Bell" on Tuesday.

"We've seen oil</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.cnbc.com/id/101485262</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T18:11:01-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>PR Newswire</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>New Alliance</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Atlas Pipeline Partners, L.P. Retains Citigroup Global Markets To Sell Its Interest In West Texas LPG Pipeline Limited Partnership</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>PHILADELPHIA, March 11, 2014 /PRNewswire/ -- Atlas Pipeline Partners, L.P. (NYSE: APL ) ("APL", "Atlas Pipeline", or the "Partnership") announced today that it has retained Citigroup Global Markets Inc. to begin a strategic review of its ownership interest in the West Texas LPG Pipeline Limited Partnership ("WTXLPG"). To the extent that Atlas Pipeline executes any transaction, the potential</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/atlas-pipeline-partners-lp-retains-citigroup-global-markets-to-sell-its-interest-in-west-texas-lpg-pipeline-limited-partnership-249634661.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T17:32:59-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Money Morning</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Activity</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron's (NYSE: CVX) Annual Analyst Meeting Warns of Lingering Shifts in LNG Prices, Oil Prices</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron (NYSE: CVX ), the nation's second-largest oil company and the world's fourth-largest energy producer by market value, cut expectations for its 2017 production by 6.1% at its annual security analyst meeting today (Tuesday), citing a drop in LNG prices and an increase in oil prices .

Over the last several months, the petrochemical company, along with industry competitors, has been</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://moneymorning.com/2014/03/11/chevrons-nyse-cvx-annual-analyst-meeting-warns-lingering-shifts-lng-prices-oil-prices/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T16:17:57-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Thomson Reuters Foundation</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>ExxonMobil seeks settlement in $800 mln Chad tax dispute</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>An ExxonMobil led XOM.N consortium in Chad is seeking an out-of-court settlement after the government filed a legal claim for more than $800 million in unpaid taxes, finance ministry sources said on Tuesday.</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.trust.org/item/20140311183926-p0yt6/?source=hptop</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T15:29:25-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Financial Post</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Activity</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Tensions between buyers and sellers could impact LNG projects, Chevron CEO says</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Oil-linked liquefied natural gas prices make the &#34;most sense&#34; for Asian buyers, but lack of consensus among buyers and sellers could impact proposed projects, Chevron Corp. chief executive says.

“There is a lot of tension right now between buyers and sellers,” John Watson, Chevron&#39;s chairman and CEO told investors Tuesday during a meeting with investors.

“Our view has been that for</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://business.financialpost.com/2014/03/11/tensions-between-buyers-and-sellers-could-impact-lng-projects-chevron-ceo-says/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T13:16:38-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>THISDAY Live</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Merger And Acquisition</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Court Fixes March 20 for Hearing Brittania-U, Chevron Suit</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>A Federal High Court sitting in Lagos has fixed March 20, 2014 for hearing of application challenging the jurisdiction of the court to entertain the suit brought before it by an indigenous oil company, Brittania-U Nigeria Limited against Chevron.

The plaintiff, Brittania-U Nigeria Limited had sought an interlocutory injunction from the court, seeking among other things the pronouncement</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.thisdaylive.com/articles/court-fixes-march-20-for-hearing-brittania-u-chevron-suit/173479/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T12:39:47-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Bloomberg.com</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Cuts Long-Term Output Target as Gas Drilling Slows</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron Corp. (CVX) , the world&#39;s fourth-largest energy producer by market value, reduced its 2017 production estimate and said it will sell $10 billion in assets during the next three years.

Chevron lowered its production forecast by 6.1 percent as it slows U.S. natural gas drilling and higher crude prices reduce its share of production in some nations, the company said during a</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2014-03-11/chevron-cuts-long-term-output-target-as-gas-drilling-slows-1-.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T11:32:29-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>The Wall Street Journal</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Expects Production to Grow Through End of Decade</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron Corp. on Tuesday said it expects increasing world-wide energy demand to prompt "significant" production growth over the rest of the decade, while costs level off.

"We believe this compelling growth profile, combined with flattening capital spending levels these next few years, should serve as a strong catalyst for value creation for our shareholders in the years ahead," Chairman</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://online.wsj.com/news/articles/SB10001424052702304250204579432942942972508?mod=WSJ_business_whatsNews&amp;mg=reno64-wsj</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T11:30:46-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>24/7 Wall St</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Plans to Get Slimmer</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>At its analyst meeting in New York Tuesday morning, Chevron Corp. (NYSE: CVX) trimmed its 2017 production forecast from 3.3 million barrels of oil equivalent per day to 3.1 million. Falling natural gas prices, higher production costs and costly project delays are getting the blame for the drop. The company also expects to boost its asset sales over the next three years from $7 billion</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://247wallst.com/energy-business/2014/03/11/chevron-plans-to-get-slimmer/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T11:25:32-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Reuters</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>UPDATE 2-Chevron cuts production outlook on delays, rising costs</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>NEW YORK, March 11 (Reuters) - Chevron Corp, the second-largest U.S. oil company, cut expectations for its 2017 production on Tuesday by 6 percent, citing lower natural gas prices, rising costs and project delays.

The company, like many of its peers, has seen mixed results from spending heavily to lift oil and natural gas production, and shareholders in the sector are pushing for more</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.reuters.com/article/2014/03/11/chevron-investor-idUSL2N0M80SU20140311</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T10:00:46-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Yahoo! Finance</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron trims production forecast on project delays, rising costs</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>NEW YORK, March 11 (Reuters) - Chevron Corp, the second-largest U.S. oil company, lowered expectations for its 2017 production on Tuesday, citing lower natural gas prices, rising costs and project delays.

The company now expects to produce 3.1 million barrels of oil equivalent per day (boe/d) by 2017.

Chevron had previously forecast 2017 production of 3.3 million boe/d.

"Our growth</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://finance.yahoo.com/news/chevron-trims-production-forecast-project-134211209.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T09:00:09-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Oil Voice</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron reaffirms strategies, highlights performance, portfolio and future growth</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Upstream financial performance leads industry, positioned to deliver growth to end of decade.

Downstream delivers competitive returns, targeting growth in petrochemicals and lubricants.

Financial strength supports high quality investment queue and growing shareholder distributions.

Chevron Corporation (NYSE: CVX) is continuing to generate industry-leading operational and</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.oilvoice.com/n/Chevron_reaffirms_strategies_highlights_performance_portfolio_and_future_growth/e0e0815a35a0.aspx</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-11T03:00:00-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Financial Times</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron raises forecast for oil price</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron, the US oil group, has raised sharply its expectation of future oil prices and cut its target for production growth, as it...</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.ft.com/cms/s/13240d08-a943-11e3-9b71-00144feab7de,s01=1.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-10T09:30:28-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>HBJ Morning Call - Bizjournals</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>From the shale boom to the growing demand that looms &#8212; the best of CERAWeek</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>The ever-growing IHS Energy CERAWeek went off smoothly in downtown Houston as energy and policy executives and experts swarmed to the area from around the world. Some of the week's highlights included:

Chevron Corp. (NYSE: CVX) Chairman and CEO John Watson is a born-and-raised "proud Californian." He offered a succinct "No" and left after being asked if the energy supermajor is</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.bizjournals.com/houston/morning_call/2014/03/from-the-shale-boom-to-the-growing-demand-that.html?ana=RSS&amp;s=article_search</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-10T07:58:34-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>AllAfrica.com</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>General Industry</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Donates Hybrid Libraries to Adamawa, Kano Schools</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Oil firm Chevron has donated hybrid libraries to two schools in Adamawa and Kano in what analysts say could be the first time children there would hold a mouse.

The hybrid libraries, equipped with VSAT internet connection, feature conventional paper and electronic books, along with customizable electronic library platform that allows teachers to digitize reading material that students</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://allafrica.com/stories/201403100705.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-09T23:28:02-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>The West Australian</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>New Alliance</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Govt flags Onslow land release (The West Australian)</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>The State Government has signed a land sale agreement with Chevron to open up housing lots in a new estate in Onslow to support the oil and gas giant's $29 billion Wheatstone LNG project.

Chevron has agreed to buy 50 lots and a 9ha site within the estate.

The company's commitment to the sale will enable LandCorp to begin work on 220 lots in stage one of the estate, providing new</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://au.news.yahoo.com/thewest/business/wa/a/21902470/govt-flags-onslow-land-release/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-09T21:02:52-04:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>World War 4 Report</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>US judge blocks enforcement of Chevron judgment</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>A judge for the US District Court for the Southern District of New York on March 4 ruled ( PDF ) that US courts may not be used to collect $9.51 billion in fines and legal fees from an Ecuadoran court's judgment against Chevron . Judge Lewis Kaplan wrote in his near 500-page ruling that the punishment inflicted against Chevron was not justified, and that the Ecuadoran court's judgement</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://ww4report.com/node/13063</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-09T01:18:26-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>The West Australian</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron spruiks social investment (The West Australian)</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>A year out from turning on the $US54 billion ($59.4 billion) Gorgon gas project on Barrow Island, operator Chevron yesterday talked up the money and effort it was pumping into WA to hold onto its "social licence to operate".

It included more than $1 billion spent on research and development in the State since 2009 - the year Gorgon was approved for development - though Chevron Australia</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://au.news.yahoo.com/thewest/latest/a/21892397/chevron-spruiks-social-investment/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-08T09:49:54-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>TheStreet.com</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Here's What Happened During the U.S. Energy Industry's Most Prestigious Conference</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>NEW YORK ( TheStreet ) -- The most powerful individuals in the energy sector converged on Houston this week to exchange ideas and address the latest industry developments.

The most prestigious energy conference in the United States, IHS's CERAWeek, featured addresses by Chevron ( CVX ) CEO John Watson, Energy Secretary Ernest Moniz, Sen. Lisa Murkowski (R., Alaska), TOTAL S.A. ( TOT )</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.thestreet.com/story/12522266/1/heres-what-happened-during-the-us-energy-industrys-most-prestigious-conference.html?cm_ven=RSSFeed</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-08T02:49:18-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>GreenIsTheNewRed.com</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Says Hell Will Freeze Over Before It Pays For Pollution</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>When 30,000 Ecuadorian villagers sued Chevron in 1993 for devastating the Amazon with 18 billion gallons of toxic wastewater, the US-based oil giant&#39;s reply was simple: “We will fight [the lawsuit] until hell freezes over,” said a representative . “And then fight it out on the ice.”

After investigators documented what they call a “Rainforest Chernobyl”&#8212;17 million gallons of spilled</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.greenisthenewred.com/blog/chevron-rico-lawsuit-ecuador/7672/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-07T17:04:21-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Reuters</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron's U.S. win in Ecuador case looms over cases elsewhere</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>NEW YORK Fri Mar 7, 2014 4:22pm EST

NEW YORK (Reuters) - Ecuadorean villagers who are trying to get billions of dollars from Chevron Corp for pollution in the Amazon jungle are ready to refocus their fight on pending suits in other countries after a setback in the United States.

A scathing judgment issued by a U.S. judge this week against their lawyer will cast a long shadow over cases</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.reuters.com/article/2014/03/07/us-chevron-ecuador-canada-idUSBREA261P820140307</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-07T16:08:07-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>News.nom.co</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Merger And Acquisition</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Man who sued Facebook's Zuckerberg must face fraud charges: judge</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Does WhatsApp deal show Facebook knows what&#39;s up?: If Facebook hopes to remain the social networking leader, CEO Mark Zuckerberg knows the company must follow the people. That realization compelled Zuckerberg to pay $19 billion for WhatsApp, a mobile . (DailyHerald.com) Read News

U.S. judge rules for Chevron in Ecuador environmental case: By Joseph Ax NEW YORK (Reuters) - An American</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.news.nom.co/man-who-sued-facebook-s-zuckerberg-must-8282662-news/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-07T15:20:50-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>petroleumworld</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>CERAWEEK: Soaring costs present concern of the oil industry</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Underneath their swagger and bravado, global energy chiefs gathered here for their annual U.S. conference expressed a palpable sense of dread over the soaring costs of their signature oil and gas projects. "All of us are facing new realities and pressures,"  John Watson , chairman and chief executive of  Chevron  Corp.</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.petroleumworld.com/storyt14030701.htm</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-07T14:12:13-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>PR Daily</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Locals don't share outsiders' rage over Chevron&#39;s post-blast pizza coupons</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron sparked considerable outrage a few weeks ago when it apologized for a very loud, very disruptive fracking well explosion in Bobtown, Pa., with coupons for free pizza .

Nearly 13,000 people have signed a MoveOn.org petition demanding a further apology for the explosion, calling the pizza coupons “an insult.” According to an Associated Press story , none of those people are</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.prdaily.com/Main/Articles/1d53442a-12f2-4f77-a890-629e76d20da2.aspx</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-07T13:30:17-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>The Heritage Foundation Blog</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron Ruling Will Strengthen Rule of Law in Ecuador</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>A New York federal court ruling this week sends a strong and positive message to Ecuador&#8212;that corrupt methods and practices that undermine the integrity of Ecuador&#39;s judicial system will not be tolerated in the United States. They should not be tolerated in Ecuador, either.

Two years ago, a court in Ecuador levied a colossal fine of nearly $19 billion (later reduced to $9.5 billion)</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://blog.heritage.org/2014/03/07/chevron-ruling-will-strengthen-rule-law-ecuador/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-07T09:42:59-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>BlackListedNews.com</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>New Alliance</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Ukraine signs $10 billion shale gas deal with Chevron</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Ukraine signed a $10 billion shale gas production-sharing agreement with U.S. Chevron ( CVX.N ) on Tuesday, another step in a drive for more energy independence from Russia .

The deal to develop its western Olesska field followed a similar shale gas agreement with Royal Dutch Shell ( RDSa.L ) in January and boosts Ukraine's leadership at a time of fraught relations with Moscow over gas?</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.blacklistednews.com/Ukraine_signs_%2410_billion_shale_gas_deal_with_Chevron/33456/0/0/0/Y/M.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-07T03:47:01-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>KansasCity.com</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron pizza 'scandal' isn't one in small town</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>News stories, TV shows and blogs &#8212; many sarcastic or outright scornful &#8212; spread the word far and wide. "Shame on you," one person wrote about the offer by Chevron Corp. "How insulting!" said another. Comedy Central's satirical "The Colbert Report" skewered it.

But the 750 or so residents of the hamlet of Bobtown? Not one has signed an online petition demanding an apology for</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.kansascity.com/2014/03/07/4871652/chevron-pizza-scandal-isnt-one.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-07T01:04:22-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Watts Up With That?</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron defeats the Greens with their own hubris</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Story submitted by Eric Worrall

James Delingpole writing for Breitbart London has published a fascinating story of how green groups were undone by their own hubris and misleading evidence in their effort to sue Chevron Oil for billions of dollars for pollution.

Thanks to Chevron&#39;s CEO John S Watson&#39;s courages decision to stand up to naked green bullying, and the arrogant stupidity of?</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://wattsupwiththat.com/2014/03/06/chevron-defeats-the-greens-with-their-own-hubris/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T21:23:51-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>The Wall Street Journal</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>How Business Can Fight Fraudulent Lawsuits</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Trial lawyers may increasingly feel the sting of the Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act.

On Tuesday, in a federal courtroom in Manhattan, U.S. District Judge Lewis Kaplan found plaintiffs lawyer Steven Donziger and his legal team had engaged in coercion, bribery, money laundering and other misconduct to obtain a $9.5 billion judgment against Chevron CVX +0.37% in an</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://online.wsj.com/news/articles/SB10001424052702304815004579419600026911302?mod=WSJ_Opinion_LEFTTopOpinion&amp;mg=reno64-wsj</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T20:06:24-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>The Wall Street Journal</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Energy Chiefs Sound Cost Alarms</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>HOUSTON&#8212;Underneath their swagger and bravado, global energy chiefs gathered here for their annual U.S. conference expressed a palpable sense of dread over the soaring costs of their signature oil and gas projects.

"All of us are facing new realities and pressures," John Watson , chairman and chief executive of Chevron Corp. CVX +0.37% , told a hotel ballroom jammed with an international</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://online.wsj.com/news/articles/SB10001424052702304732804579423473478126620?mod=WSJ_US_LatestHeadlines&amp;mg=reno64-wsj</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T18:15:47-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Prensa Latina News Agency</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Other Countries to Implement Ecuadorian Ruling Agaisnt Chevron</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>06 de marzo de 2014, 17:01Quito, Mar 5 (Prensa Latina) The lawyers of those affected by the oil company Chevron said today that the adverse judgment issued by a U.S. judge will not prevent the implementation by other countries of the ruling issued by an Ecuadorian court.

In this regard, Lawyer Juan Pablo Sáenz said that the verdict of the U.S. judge is applied only in the territory of</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.plenglish.com/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=2448811&amp;Itemid=1</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T17:24:43-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>SFGate</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Big hole in big-oil lawsuit</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>The story starts with a former journalist and Harvard Law graduate who wanted to improve conditions for Ecuadoran people living in Amazon rain forest polluted by a big oil company. In 2011, attorney Steven Donziger won a $9.5 billion judgment against Chevron Corp. But don't expect a happy ending for his clients.

Tuesday, New York federal judge Lewis Kaplan ruled that the Chevron</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.sfgate.com/opinion/saunders/article/Big-hole-in-big-oil-lawsuit-5291875.php</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T15:27:26-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>TechBeat - BusinessWeek</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>The Chevron RICO Ruling and Abortion Clinic Protests</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>At the heart of the matter is whether the racketeering law permits trial judges to impose injunctions</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2014-03-06/how-the-chevron-rico-ruling-relates-to-abortion-clinic-protests</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T11:55:08-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>NewsBusters Blog</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Evening News Shows Ignore Chevron's Win: Ecuador Ruling 'Fraud'</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>In a huge victory for the second-largest U.S. oil company, a U.S. district judge ruled March 4, that a $9.5 billion award against Chevron by an Ecuadorean court was “obtained by corrupt means.” The massive figure had been lowered by Ecuador&#39;s highest court in 2013 after an earlier decision against Chevron of $19 billion.

The broadcast networks took no notice of the decision and</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://newsbusters.org/blogs/julia-seymour/2014/03/06/evening-news-shows-ignore-chevrons-win-ecuador-ruling-fraud</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T10:57:55-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>EcoWatch</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>U.S. Judge Sides With Chevron in Case Against Ecuadorians, Allows Oil Giant to Evade Justice</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Amazon Watch stands with Ecuadorian communities in rejecting a misguided judgment delaying justice for some 30,000 indigenous people and farmers who continue to suffer from the company&#39;s toxic legacy in the Amazon rainforest . The decision&#8212;handed down yesterday by New York District Court Judge Lewis Kaplan&#8212;also underscores the threat that well-financed corporations pose ?to? justice and</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://ecowatch.com/2014/03/05/chevron-case-against-ecuadorians-oil-giant-evades-justice/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=chevron-case-against-ecuadorians-oil-giant-evades-justice</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T05:48:39-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>National Public Radio, Inc.</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>U.S. Judge Sides With Chevron In Amazon Pollution Case</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Audio for this story from Morning Edition will be available at approximately 9:00 a.m. ET.

He ruled the $9.5 billion verdict against Chevron for oil pollution in the Amazon was obtained illegally and is unenforceable. For more, David Green talks to Paul Barrett of Bloomberg Businessweek.</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.npr.org/2014/03/06/286646472/u-s-judge-sides-with-chevron-in-amazon-pollution-case?ft=1&amp;f=1006</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T03:23:14-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Management Change</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Atlas Energy, L.P.: 8-K Filing 2014-03-04</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Atlas Energy, L.P. Item 5.02. Departure of Directors or Certain Officers; Election of Directors; Appointment of Certain Officers; Compensatory Arrangements of Certain Officers
Effective March 4, 2014, the Board of Directors (the "Board") of Atlas Energy GP, LLC, the general partner of Atlas Energy, L.P. (the "Partnership"), approved the appointment of Jeffrey Kupfer to the Board. Mr.</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/1347218/000118143114010616/rrd404519.htm</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T02:53:35-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Omaha World-Herald</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Chevron legal victory boosts fight against Ecuador claims</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Since losing a $19 billion judgment in an Ecuadorean court three years ago, Chevron has drawn the condemnation of human rights and environmental activists by refusing to pay anything in fines or accept blame for polluting the Ecuadorean rain forest.

The award against Chevron was one of the largest judgments ever imposed by a court for environmental pollution, and it appeared to pit a</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.omaha.com/article/20140306/MONEY/140309246</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T02:10:03-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Circle of Blue</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>The Stream, March 5: U.S. Judge Finds Corruption in Ecuador&#39;s Decision on Chevron Water Pollution Case</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Pollution A federal judge in the United States ruled that actions by lawyers representing plaintiffs in a decades-long Ecuador water pollution case were corrupt, making it less likely that Chevron&#8212;the oil company accused of pollution&#8212;will end up paying the $US 9.5 billion fine ordered last year by Ecuador&#39;s highest court, The New York Times reported.</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.circleofblue.org/waternews/2014/the-stream/stream-march-5-u-s-judge-finds-corruption-ecuadors-decision-chevron-water-pollution-case/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=stream-march-5-u-s-judge-finds-corruption-ecuadors-decision-chevron-water-pollution-case</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T01:04:26-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Bloomberg.com</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Management Change</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Argentina Oil&#39;s Bonanza Helping Too Few Led by Political Friends</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Chevron and YPF are drilling in Argentina on the world's fourth-largest shale oil reserve.

Chevron and YPF are drilling in Argentina on the world's fourth-largest shale oil reserve.

Chevron and YPF are drilling in Argentina on the world's fourth-largest shale oil reserve. Close

Jose Luis Manzano, a former house speaker, controls companies that won 33 oil leases in six</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2014-03-06/argentina-oil-s-bonanza-helping-too-few-led-by-political-friends.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T00:17:13-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Hydrocarbon Processing</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Executive Quote</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>CERAWeek &#39;14: Chevron CEO sees &#34;new reality&#34; in project pricing</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>There is no shortage of global energy resources, Chevron's CEO said at the IHS CERAWeek 2014 conference. However, the economics to develop big projects are increasing.

HOUSTON -- John Watson, chairman and CEO of Chevron, delivered Tuesday's keynote address at the IHS CERAWeek 2014 conference. In his remarks, Watson reviewed the last few years of the oil and gas (O&amp;G) industry.

?</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://www.hydrocarbonprocessing.com/Article/3315705/Heat-Transfer/CERAWeek-14-Chevron-CEO-sees-new-reality-in-project-pricing.html</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                     <NewsDetails>
                        <PublishedDateTimestamp>2014-03-06T00:08:39-05:00</PublishedDateTimestamp>
                        <SourceDescription>Oil Change</SourceDescription>
                        <CategoryText>Regulation Or Litigation</CategoryText>
                        <TitleText>Activists Criticise &#34;Misguided&#34; Chevron Court Ruling</TitleText>
                        <ContentText>Indigenous rights groups reacted angrily yesterday to what they labelled as a &#34;misguided judgement&#34; by a New York District Court Judge, Lewis Kaplan, who ruled that lawyers representing Amazonian Indians had used &#34;corrupt means&#34; and &#34;fraud&#34; to win a legal case against Chevron in Ecuador.

The dramatic judgement is the latest setback for 30,000 indigenous Indians in their decades long</ContentText>
                        <WebPageURL>http://priceofoil.org/2014/03/05/activists-criticise-misguided-chevron-court-ruling/</WebPageURL>
                     </NewsDetails>
                  </News>
              